abc-directory.com 2013-05-20

# Privacy Policy : ABC Directory - Free Web Directory - Business Web Resources

Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of all visitors to our website.

You can access, browse our web site without disclosing your personal data. We do not collect any personal data from our visitors when they use our services.

Our Web server automatically receives anonymous "general usage data" which could include a record of which pages at our website visitors frequent the most. This information helps us determine which type of software and computing resources are most popular with our viewers and allows us to serve them better.

In order to serve advertisements to this site, third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" or web beacons on your browser. If we are utilizing an Advertising Network that sets cookies, we would not receive or collect any of the information. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

This website provides external links to other websites. We are not responsible and cannot control the content and security of other sites you visit once you leave our website.

We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. We will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such changes here or on our home page. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit our site. For additional information or question, please contact us.
